Review
Truly the perfect girlfriend
Send
Cancel
Yes?
Mizuhara? What does she want?!
I lost my key.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"The Return of the Girlfriend"
Huh? Your key?
R-Really? That's pretty yikes.
Yeah.
What's going on?!
Her key? Mizuhara... lost her key?
So she can't get into her apartment?
But why'd she ring my doorbell?
What's she trying to say?
What's she expecting from me?
Do you mind?
It looks like the landlord
won't be back until tomorrow.
I rang their bell, but no response.
I called my realtor, too,
but working hours are long over.
I must've lost it at the batting center.
I called them, too, but nobody
answered. For crying out loud.
Your place is always so messy.
Oh, sorry, were you about to sleep?
N-Not at all! I'm a night owl!
Oh? That's a relief.
She waltzed into my apartment! QED!
She's locked out
=
She has nowhere
to go tonight
She's locked out, which means
she has nowhere to go tonight!
× Next-door
neighbor
I'm her next-door neighbor.
÷ Waltzed
in casually
Which leads us to the only
possible conclusion!
Find a conclusion
based on the
above formula.
She wants to spend the night at my place!
QED! It couldn't be anything else!
But can I say it? Do I have it in me?
Can I really ask Mizuhara,
"Hey, why don't you just sleep over?"
But look at the time. I can't
throw her out onto the street.
My neighbor... Yes, my neighbor's in trouble!
Is this
a train?
If I ignored her, I wouldn't be a man!
Cute
It's not like anything will happen.
I just... I just gotta
let her stay the night!
I, Kinoshita Kazuya, male,
will make the offer of a lifetime!
D-D-D-Do you wanna...
stay the...
Huh? The balcony?
I'm pretty sure I locked up,
but let me try, just in case.
If it's open, that solves everything.
S-Sure.
The saddest
"Sure"
in Nerima
QED, my ass!
I mean, yeah...
There's no way she'd ever wanna
spend the night at my place...
U-Uh...
wiggle
Mizuhara... san?
Hold up. Am I allowed to look?
Her ass is totally
making eye contact with me!
swirl
Okay, yeah, I can't get
a good look from here.
Why is the lock
on the other side?
Meanwhile, I'm getting too good a look.
Maybe if I lean over a little more...
Hup.
Huh? Hey, watch out!
FREEZE
FLUFF
I grabbed her ass!!
H-Hey! Where do you think you're touching?!
But you were about to fall!
fluff
rub
There are plenty of other
places you could've grabbed!
fluff
rub
L-Like where?!
fluff
rub
Eek! Hey, hands off!
Like my waist! My waist!
Y-Your waist?
Like, here?
WOB
The waist's no better!
Soft
and
plump!?
Sweat
Okay, I checked!
So let me go!
S-Sorry.
Wait, not so suddenly...
Watch out! Hey!
M-Mizuhara.
I'm so close to her...
This range is lethal.
We haven't been this close since...
Yeah, point-blank Mizuhara is a bomb!
Her long eyelashes, round eyes,
and even her skin glinting
with sweat is super sexy.
Damn, Mizuhara's hot!
Don't be stupid!
She's gonna punch me again!
To the Moon!
Get off.
Get off me, please.
Mizuhara...?
Th-The mailman, maybe?
This late, though?
Who could it be?
DOOM
Hey, aren't you going to answer?
Shh! Shhhhhh!
It's M... Mami-chan!
Wha?!
Why's Mami-san here?
Did you two make plans?
A-As if!
I may have given
her my address
at some point
This is the first time
she's come to my place!
This is bad news.
If she sees me here...
I-I know that!
Why? To what end?
What is Mami-chan doing here?
She always refused to come
over every time I asked...
So why now?
She knows that Mizuhara's
a rental girlfriend.
It all pisses me off just a teensy bit.
If she sees us like this, I'm dead!
Gulp...
Just gotta pretend I'm not home.
The door's unlocked!
What? Seriously?
Right! I left it unlocked
after Mizuhara showed up!
This way!
Wai...
My shoes!
Mine
O-Oh, right.
Please, leave!
Go away!
Kazu-kun?
Are you home?
Your door's unlocked, you know.
Did he go shopping?
Talk about careless.
It's over...
It's all over!
wobble  wobble
tremble  wobble  wobble
tremble  tremble
I thought
I was done for!!
I demand an explanation!
Why did Mami-san come here?
D-Don't ask me!
She doesn't know I was watching
the two of you the other day.
Maybe she wanted to talk about that?
Tap
Anyway, I was too thoughtless.
I shouldn't have entered your apartment.
Tap
I'm never
coming in
here again!!
Tap
W-Wait up!
She could still be out there!
Good point.
Nod
Shopping?
Leaving the lights on,
and the door unlocked?
It's not impossible, I guess?
Kinoshita Kazuya
I just dropped by 'cause I was in the area.
I don't know if it's worth calling him...
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Are you home?
You're kidding me.
The silence is killing me!
And Mizuhara's been standing the whole time.
Is she wary of me because of what happened?
There's too much going on.
I don't know what to talk about.
I-I wonder what Mami-chan was here for.
Riiiight?
Right?
There's no point in thinking about it.
We just have to be glad she didn't see us.
Talk about calm...
She's always been a needy girl.
I really find that hard to believe.
But...
Why did she come to me?
Sure, our balconies are connected,
but couldn't she have gone to
her parents or friends instead?
ba-dump
Maybe that's how much she trusts me?
Okay, I should get going.
Surely she's left by now.
Oh, let me check outside.
Phew.
No sign of her.
Oh, look!
The landlord's back.
G-Good news.
Goodnight, then. Thanks for having me.
Please, please, be that for Chizuru.
L-Let me know if you ever need help!
I-I know we nearly got in trouble this time,
but stuff happens all the time in life.
If you can't turn to your parents or friends,
I'll do everything I can as your neighbor.
They're gone.
My parents... are gone.
Mizuhara...
My father left when I was little.
My mom and I went to live
with my grandparents.
But my mom died soon after,
and so did my grandpa,
when I was in high school.
So my "family" is just my grandma and me.
Come to think of it...
Jeez, Grandma. You haven't
replaced the water in the vase.
It never felt like her family was around.
I made a promise...
I promised my grandpa that I
would become an actress one day.
So I at least want my grandma
to see me performing on screen.
That's my dream.
Made you cringe?
The girl you're paying to go on
dates with is nothing special.
I'm a failed actress...
Just a girl in college who's still
clinging to a childish dream.
So, honestly, don't expect too much from me.
Sorry about everything tonight.
Goodnight.
I guess I lucked out.
Both my parents are still alive.
And even now, if I go back home,
they'll welcome me back and feed me.
It's hard to believe, but my Gran
doted all over me when I was a baby.
His eyebrows are just like his grandpa's!
There, there, my boy!
I'm an only child,
so she was gung-ho about giving me,
the successor, some "early education."
She bought me all sorts of toys and stuff.
Here's a bridge!
Now you can link two structures!
Mom, it's too early for him.
Om nom
He's chewing on the train...
They say a kid's IQ is
set by the age of five!
I don't know if I lived up
to her hopes, though...
Seriously, though, compared to you,
I've lived a carefree life.
What? Are you bragging?
S-Sorry
U-Uh, no. What I'm trying to say is...
All that said, I sometimes think about
how my future's set in stone already.
You mean...
Oh, uh, I'm not against taking
over the store or anything.
It's not like I have any
concrete goals, anyway.
Even running a convenience store would be
too good a life for the likes of me, seriously.
And, of course, I feel indebted
to my family for raising me,
and I wanna repay them for
taking such good care of me.
Nagomi                         Sake
I was born into this family,
so I believe it's my purpose
in life to take over the store.
And that's fine by me. Just fine.
But...
But one day, she'll surely need
someone who sees her for who she is.
You just look so cool in my eyes.
I don't know, like... you're pursuing
your dreams with all you've got,
and you'll do whatever it takes.
See her for who she is? Be there for her?
I bawled my eyes out watching your play, too.
This isn't about fanciful ideas like those.
I just wanna see you fulfill your dream.
I really, really do.
So I wanna be there forever... by your side.
Is that too much to ask?
"Forever"?
Er, wait!
Blush
Sweat
Of all the creepy things to say!
Stupid.
Stu—
If you want me to be with you,
I can't very well refuse.
Mizuhara?
That's a rental girlfriend's job.
Bye.
That night, the sight of Mizuhara
leaving was etched into my eyes,
leaving me unable to sleep.
I know she's lived a life hundreds
of times harder than mine,
and gone through so much pain...
If you want me to be with you,
I can't very well refuse.
I don't know if that came from the heart.
I don't know if you meant it,
or if it was just lip service.
But my feelings are real.
It doesn't matter if you're a rental
girlfriend, or just my neighbor.
That's a rental girlfriend's job.
It doesn't matter if I'm just your
client, or your boyfriend.
Even if this were all to come to an
end someday, I wanna be there for you.
I want you to know that
that isn't lip service.
I mean it, from the heart.
M-Mizuhara!
Crap, I stopped!
Glance    Glance
Nobody's
around, right!?
Hmm...
You don't know her! You don't know her!
Dazed...
Economics Department Special Seminar Numbering
Okay, yeah, I'm down bad.
What is wrong with me?
She's a rental girlfriend, y'know.
I'm making my feelings obvious...
showing no self-control.
But there's something I don't get.
I feel like Mizuhara knows
I'm in love with her.
"We feel nothing for each other."
That was what our relationship was
built on, and what kept it ticking.
If she finds out I've
actually fallen for her,
I pose a risk to her as a rental girlfriend.
She could easily tell her agency
and break off all contact forever.
So then, why is she so nice to me?
Kazuya-kun, I feel the same way...
What am I thinking?!
Grah!
She finally came around and
said we could be "neighbors."
If I get carried away, things
will go right back to square one!
Wha!?
Creep.
This is all Mizuhara's
fault for being so cute.
Kazu-kun.
Bob
M-Mami-chan?!
Whatcha hiding?
Ugh! I overreacted!
Swirl
She did come over last night and all...
Does she wanna talk about that?
Swirl
Do you have a minute?
Kazu-kun!
Wh-What's up, Mami-chan?
Are you panicking about something?
Nah, I just didn't know you'd
be joining me for the preview.
Huh... Does that mean you don't
know what happens, either?
N-No idea.
I'll give you two hints.
"Naked" and "Sleepover."
Buck naked, sleeping together?!
You're so funny, Kazu-kun.
Anyway, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend...
"Night...
...and Girlfriend."
Oh, Kazu-kun, you have a nosebleed!
"Night and Girlfriend"
Virgins are so lol.